Guide to the Gay men's popular fiction collection, 1931-1992
Gay men's popular fiction collection, 1931-1992
- D'Arcangelo, Angelo, Sookey, Olympia Press, TC-465, 1969 (Box 39)
- D'Etamge, Jonathon, Dark Brotherhood, Blueboy Library, 80045, 1977 (Box 8)
- Daimler, Harriet, Innocence, Olympia Press, OPS 6, 1970 (Box 38)
- Dale, Dick, The Cruising Class, Corinth Pubns., NB 1860, 1967 (Box 14)
- Dale, Dick, Gay But Not Happy, Corinth Pubns., CB 552, 1968 (Box 43)
- Dale, Dick, The Fag End, Greenleaf Classics, AB 442, 1968 (Box 20)
- Dale, Dick, Callboy, Greenleaf Classics, AB 447, 1968 (Box 20)
- Dale, Dick, Gay Paragon, Greenleaf Classics, AB 452, 1968 (Box 20)
- Dale, Dick, Gay On The Range, Phenix Publishers, CB 547, 1967 (Box 43)
- Dale, Dick, Four-Way Gay, Phenix Publishers, CB 557, 1968 (Box 43)
- Dale, Dick, The Price Of Pansies, Phenix Publishers, LL 768, 1968 (Box 44)
- Dale, Dick, Mr. Fancy-Panties, Phenix Publishers, LL 775, 1968 (Box 44)
- Dalles, Elmer, Jock Man, P. E. C., FL 75, 1970 (Box 52)
- Dalton, Anthony, Baby Face, 101 Enterprises, 101-4, 1967 (Box 39)
- Dalton, Rick, No Middle Way, Corsair Pubns., 211, 1968 (Box 15)
- Damon, Buster, Mostly Male, E.L. Publishing Co., G-1, 1970 (Box 15)
- Danbury, Dylan, He's Gay And Married, Paramount, SL 515, 1971 (Box 40)
- Dandridge, Guy, Jerry And Jim, Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1967 (Box 27)
- Dandridge, Guy, A Bible, A Book And A Boy, Guild Press Ltd., RC 109, 1971 (Box 28)
- Dandridge, Guy, Gay Patrolman, Guild Press Ltd., RC 119, 1971 (Box 28)
- Dandridge, Guy, Ready Willing And Able, Guild Press Ltd., RC 122, 1971 (Box 28)
- Dandridge, Guy, Boy's Camp, Guild Press Ltd., RC-121, 1971 (Box 90)
- Daniels, Gordon, Black Angel, Greenleaf Classics, PR 364, 1972 (Box 48)
- Daniels, Harold, The Snatch, Dell Publishing Co., A170, 1958 (Box 90)
- Daniels, Joe, Cellblock Rape, Timely Books, -0-, 1971 (Box 90)
- Danom, Jack, Barbarians, Blueboy Library, BB 122, 1978 (Box 11)
- Dante, Mark, Beware Of Greeks, Surree Ltd, HIS 69426, 1981 (Box 79)
- Danton, Frank C., The Fist Club, Star Dist., HS 506, 1977 (Box 62)
- Dark, Jon, Satan's Victor, GX, Inc., TC 246, 1972 (Box 31)
- Dark, Jon, Devil At China Cove, GX, Inc., TC 260, 1973 (Box 31)
- Darren, Jason, Trucking Sucker, Rough Trade, RT 439, n.d. (Box 55)
- David, Benjamin, Butting In, Surrey House, HIS 06967, 1973 (Box 71)
- David, Clif, Christopher Superstud, Ophelia Press, OPH-267, 1972 (Box 40)
- Davidson, Chris, Caves Of Iron, Greenleaf Classics, AB 403, 1967 (Box 20)
- Davidson, Chris, Buffy And The Holy Quest, Greenleaf Classics, AB 433, 1968 (Box 20)
- Davidson, Chris, Buffy Rides Again, Greenleaf Classics, AB 454, 1968 (Box 20)
- Davidson, Chris, Go Down, Aaron, Greenleaf Classics, EL 376, 1967 (Box 23)
- Davidson, Chris, A Different Drum, Greenleaf Classics, EL 381, 1967 (Box 24)
- Davidson, Chris, The Virgin Eater, Greenleaf Classics, GL 107, 1969 (Box 25)
- Davidson, Chris, The Golden Tuft, Greenleaf Classics, GL 124, 1969 (Box 26)
- Davidson, Chris, Lay Them Straight, Greenleaf Classics, GL 130, 1969 (Box 26)
- Davidson, Chris, The Fellows Backstage, Phenix Publishers, CB 549, 1968 (Box 43)
- Davidson, Chris, The Last Cruise, Phenix Publishers, LL 735, 1967 (Box 44)
- Davidson, Chris, The Gay Gods, Phenix Publishers, LL 772, 1968 (Box 44)
- Davidson, Chris, Song Of Alexander, Phenix Publishers, PR 217, 1969 (Box 44)
- Davies, John, Leather Bound & Beaten, Rough Trade, RT 437, n.d. (Box 55)
- Davis, Corey, Male Box, Eros Publishing, GGs-104, 1973 (Box 16)
- Davis, Roger, Always A Stranger, Hillman Books, 196, 1961 (Box 33)
- Davis, William, The Polaroid Club Book Ii, Tiburon Publishing Co., LLP 203, 1970 (Box 87)
- Davy S., Gay Vampire, 101 Enterprises, 101-42, 1969 (Box 40)
- Dayton, Gary, Gary's Gay Odyssey, Arena, PF-101, 1983 (Box 3)
- Dayton, Gary, Hard Driver, Arena, PF-121, 1984 (Box 3)
- De Mejo, Oscar, Diary Of A Nun, Pyramid Books, F-959, 1955 (Box 53)
- de Musset, Alfred, Gamiani, Pendulum Books, 036, 1968 (Box 43)
- de Sicca, Roberto, The Golden Infidels, Nordisk Bladcentral, SVEA 35, 1969 (Box 36)
- DeAguilar, Thomas, Daddy's Tasty Chicken, Surrey House, HIS 69132, 1975 (Box 72)
- Dean, Douglas, Sidewalk Salesman, Greenleaf Classics, PR 305, 1971 (Box 46)
- Dean, Douglas, Windows And Mirrors Vol 1, Greenleaf Classics, PR 327, 1971 (Box 47)
- Dean, Douglas, Windows And Mirrors Vol 2, Greenleaf Classics, PR 328, 1971 (Box 47)
- Dean, Douglas, A Father In Shadows, Greenleaf Classics, PR 333, 1971 (Box 47)
- Dean, Douglas, One For The Money, Greenleaf Classics, PR 342, 1972 (Box 47)
- Dean, Douglas, An Exceptional Young Man, Greenleaf Classics, PR 382, 1972 (Box 48)
- Dean, Douglas, Madder Music, Stronger Wine, Phenix Publishers, PR 242, 1969 (Box 45)
- Dean, Douglas, A Stud For All Seasons, Phenix Publishers, PR 260, 1970 (Box 45)
- Dean, Douglas, This Flesh Could Melt, Phenix Publishers, PR 288, 1970 (Box 46)
- Dean, Douglas, Twin Sinners, Phenix Publishers, Ltd., PR256, 1970 (Box 90)
- Deering, Mark, Backroom Hunk, Surey Books, AGR 117, 1984 (Box 68)
- Defoe, Terry, Whipping Boy, Rough Trade, RT421, n.d. (Box 90)
- Delacourt, George, Frontier Boys, Greenleaf Classics, PR 323, 1971 (Box 47)
- Delacourt, George, The Fall Guy, Greenleaf Classics, PR 329, 1971 (Box 47)
- Delacourt, George, The Cabin Cruiser, Greenleaf Classics, PR 351, 1972 (Box 47)
- Delrook, L.M., Semper Fidelis, Blueboy Library, BB 105, 1978 (Box 11)
- Dennis, Marley, Teachin' The Chicken, Surree Ltd, HIS 69200, 1977 (Box 75)
- Dennis, Marley, Hard On His Buddy, Surree Ltd, SS 007, 1975 (Box 84)
- Denon, Serg, The Way Of Male And Female, Pendulum Books, 036, 1968 (Box 43)
- Dent, Lester, Cry At Dusk, Fawcett, 247, 1952 (Box 17)
- Derwent, Justin A., Flaming Faggot, Continental Classics, CC-242, 1969 (Box 14)
- Desmond, Robert, Professional Charmer, Pendulum Books, -0-, 1967 (Box 43)
- Deutsch, Deborah, The Flaming Heart, Paperback Library, 54-906, 1958 (Box 41)
- Dexter, John, The Self Lover, Corinth Pubns., SR 603, 1966 (Box 14)
- Dexter, John, The Gay Ones, Corinth Pubns., SR 605, 1966 (Box 15)
- Diamond, Gregg, The Brotherhood, Rough Trade, RT 427, n.d. (Box 54)
- Dibner, Martin, The Deep Six, Tower Publications, 44-542, 1953 (Box 87)
- DiCarlo, Manny, Rigid And Ready!, Surree Ltd, HIS 69148, 1975 (Box 73)
- Dick, John, Blue-Blood Stud, Surree House, HIS 69211, 1977 (Box 75)
- Dickerson, Vic, Hairport, Surrey House, HIS 06908, 1971 (Box 69)
- Dickson, Burton, Peacock Blue Batik, Phenix Publishers, PR 271, 1970 (Box 45)
- Dickson, Paul, Gay Boy Returns, PAD Library, PL 522, 1966 (Box 40)
- Dillon, Allan, Hard And Heated, Star Dist., BD 1003, n.d. (Box 58)
- DiLuna, Martin, Basket Boy, Greenleaf Classics, GL 136, 1969 (Box 26)
- Dix, E. Rex, Sausages And Buns, Surrey House, HIS 06942, 1972 (Box 70)
- Dix, E. Rex, Dick Docs, Surrey House, HIS 06984, 1974 (Box 71)
- Dixard, Bruce, Hard To Love, Spartacus Books, SB-108, 1975 (Box 17)
- Dixon, Arnold, Sheep Boy, 101 Enterprises, 101-24, 1967 (Box 40)
- Dixon, Arnold, Glory Hole Hustler, 101 Enterprises, 101-23, 1968 (Box 40)
- Dixon, Arnold, Geisha Boys, 101 Enterprises, 101-28, 1968 (Box 40)
- Dixon, Arnold, The Young And The Bad, 101 Enterprises, 101-29, 1968 (Box 40)
- Dixon, Junior, Goldenrod, Surrey House, MH 437, 1974 (Box 82)
- Dodd, Sam, Donnie And Clyde, Phenix Publishers, LL 760, 1968 (Box 44)
- Dodson, Victor, Black & Gay, Barclay House, 7067, 1969 (Box 6)
- Donaldson, Alan, Teenage Jocks, Star Dist., Club 113, 1973 (Box 59)
- Donom, Jack, Coming Weekend, Blueboy Library, BB 108, 1978 (Box 11)
- Donom, Jack, Neptune Letters, Blueboy Library, BB 111, 1978 (Box 11)
- Donom, Jack, Fatasex Boys, Blueboy Library, BB 116, 1978 (Box 11)
- Donom, Jack, Back Pack Boys, Blueboy Library, BB 121, 1978 (Box 11)
- Donom, Jack, Porno Boys, Numbers, 10014, 1978 (Box 37)
- Donom, Jack, Fantasex Boys, Numbers, ND 9, 1978 (Box 37)
- Dorian, Lee, The Anatomy Of A Homosexual, L.S. Publications, IMP 718, 1965 (Box 34)
- Dorian, Lee, The Young Homosexual, L.S. Publications, IMP 730, 1965 (Box 34)
- Dorian, Lee, Portrait Of A Homosexual, L.S. Publications, NT 803, 1967 (Box 34)
- Dorian, Lee, The Other Men, Viceroy Books, VP 218, 1966 (Box 88)
- Dorn, Philip S., Gay And Proud, Neptune Readers, NR-104, 1970 (Box 36)
- Douglas, Dean, Man Divided, Fawcett, 407, 1954 (Box 17)
- Douglas, Ray, Jr., Wandering In Twilight, National Library Books, NLB-113, 1968 (Box 36)
- Douglas, Ray, Jr., Passion to Disaster, National Library Books, 115, 1969 (Box 95)
- Douglas, Rick, Men Together, Timely Books, -0-, 1971 (Box 87)
- Douglass, Michael, Take It As It Comes, Midwood, M-195-65, 1971 (Box 35)
- Dowd, Harrison, The Night Air, Avon, AT 52, 1950 (Box 5)
- Doyle, Patrick, The Underbrush Boys, Brandon House, 6127, 1970 (Box 13)
- Doyle, Patrick, The Male Stem, Greenleaf Classics, GL 111, 1969 (Box 25)
- Doyle, Patrick, Cherry Rosebud, Greenleaf Classics, GL 122, 1969 (Box 25)
- Doyle, Patrick, Journey To Eros, Greenleaf Classics, PR 348, 1972 (Box 47)
- Doyle, Patrick, One Man's Meat, Greenleaf Classics, PR 389, 1973 (Box 48)
- Doyle, Patrick, All-American Stud, Parisian Press, P 222, 1972 (Box 42)
- Doyle, Patrick, Red, Parisian Press, P 238, 1972 (Box 42)
- Doyle, Patrick, The Staff, Phenix Publishers, PR 223, 1969 (Box 44)
- Doyle, Patrick, The Three-Dollar Bill, Phenix Publishers, PR 235, 1969 (Box 44)
- Doyle, William (with Scott O'Dell)Man Alone, Bantam Books, 1247, 1953 (Box 95)
- Drew, Dennis, Like Father Like Son, P. E. C., HES 102, 1967 (Box 53)
- Driver, Carl, Fo'c'sle Boy, Barclay House, 7056, 1969 (Box 6)
- Driver, Carl, Sex Arena, Cameo Library, 8014, 1969 (Box 13)
- Driver, Carl, Once A Knight, Greenleaf Classics, GL 123, 1969 (Box 25)
- Driver, Carl, The Soldier Boys, Greenleaf Classics, PR 388, 1972 (Box 48)
- Driver, Carl, Gay Cruise, P. E. C., FL 67, 1970 (Box 52)
- Driver, Carl, Gay Cruise, P. E. C., FL 23, n. d. (Box 51)
- Driver, Carl, Robbie, Parisian Press, P 202, 1971 (Box 41)
- Driver, Carl, Made With Clay, Pendulum Books, 0431, 1970 (Box 43)
- Driver, Carl, The War Lovers, Greenleaf Classics, PR358, 1972 (Box 90)
- Driver, Jack, Caught In The Middle, Blueboy Library, BB 117, 1978 (Box 11)
- Drummond, William, Victim, Transworld Publishers, SN 1035, 1961 (Box 87)
- Drury, Sean, Cops And Bobbers, GX, Inc., TC 233, n.d. (Box 30)
- Dubus, Andre, The Lieutenant, Dell Publishing Co., 4779, 1967 (Box 90)
- Dukahz, Casimir, The Asbestos Diary, Tower Publications, Inc., 45-985, 1966 (Box 94)
- Dukes, Roger, Gridiron Meat, Star Dist., SS-1015, 1977 (Box 66)
- Duncan, James, Pickin' The Chicken, Surrey House, MH 473, 1975 (Box 83)
- Dune, M. Ryan, Gat Temptations, Tai Pan Publications, 818, n.d. (Box 87)
- Dunn, Barry, Banged And Blown Behind Bars, Greenleaf Classics, AC 305, 1983 (Box 23)
- Dunn, Barry, Jock Mates, Greenleaf Classics, AC 346, 1985 (Box 23)
- Dunn, Mark, Queer Guise, P. E. C., FL 21, 1967 (Box 50)
- Dunn, Mark, Gay Sadist, Regency, 1021, 1970 (Box 54)
- Dunn, Mark, Live Bait, P.E.C., FL-30, 1968 (Box 90)
- Dunsmore, Six, Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1966 (Box 27)
- DuVal, Eric, Homo Sap, Private Editions Books, PE 347, 1965 (Box 48)
- Earth, R. O., Gay Blade, GX, Inc., TC 271, 1973 (Box 32)
- Eaton, Billy, Gay Navy Blue, Valley Circle Pubn., SV 111, 1972 (Box 88)
- Eaton, Jerry, Mouth Man, Surrey House, HIS 69126, 1974 (Box 72)
- Ebbing, I. V., Sherbet And Sodomy, Olympia Press, TC-509, 1971 (Box 39)
- Eberhard, Paul, Road Gang, Rough Trade, RT 428, n.d. (Box 54)
- Ecker, B.A., Independence Day, Avon, 0-380-82990-8-225, 1983 (Box 4)
- Editor, Panthology One, Spartacus, -0-, 1981 (Box 58)
- Edmunds, E. B., Unknown To The Crowd, Phenix Publishers, PR 240, 1969 (Box 45)
- Edwards, Dick, Super S*T*U*D*, Surrey House, HIS 06920, 1972 (Box 69)
- Edwards, Mark, Cherry Cop, Hamilton House, RAM 10-109, 1975 (Box 32)
- Elliot, Bruce, The Potency Clinic, Bleecker Street Press, -0-, 1978 (Box 95)
- Ellis, Alden, Fag Vet's Practice, unknown, -0-, 1968 (Box 89)
- Ellis, Cliff, The Fist-Fits, Numbers, 10007, 1978 (Box 37)
- Ellis, Cliff, Coach Brown's Little Boys, Star Dist., WB 119, 1975 (Box 68)
- Ericks, Larry, Hard Teacher, Surrey Ltd, SS 014, 1975 (Box 84)
- Ericson, Roger, The Sophisticated Stud, Star Dist., Club 125, 1973 (Box 60)
- Erikson, Gunnar, Homo Hostage, P. E. C., FL 97, 1971 (Box 52)
- Esbee, W., Jimmy, Parisian Press, P 208, 1972 (Box 41)
- Esbee, W., Prickly Heat, XXX Inc., GW 130, n.d. (Box 18)
- Esse, Jay, Wild From The Farm, Parisian Press, P 235, 1972 (Box 42)
- Evans, Dale, Bitch Boy, P. E. C., FL 84, 1970 (Box 52)
- Evans, Dan, Glory Hole, unknown, -0-, n.d. (Box 89)
- Evans, Daniel, Glory Hole, P. E. C., FL 56, 1969 (Box 51)
- Evans, Daniel, Glory Hole, P. E. C., FL 44, 1968 (Box 51)
- Evans, Donald, Mr. Muscle Boy, Selbee Publications, -0-, 1965 (Box 57)
- Evans, Donald, The Gay Jungle, Selbee Publications, -0-, 1965 (Box 57)
- Evans, Donald, Beach Boy, Selbee Publications, -0-, 1966 (Box 57)
- Evans, Donald, Male Madame, Selbee Publications, -0-, 1966 (Box 57)
- Evans, Gene, Murder On Queer Street, Brandon House, 3044, 1968 (Box 12)
- Evans, Gene, Homo Hunt, Cameo Library, 8004, 1969 (Box 13)
- Evans, Gene, The Carnal Pleasures, Gay Parisian Press, GPP 111, 1970 (Box 19)
- Evans, Gene, Faint Heart Ne'er Won..., Phenix Publishers, PR 246, 1970 (Box 45)
- Evans, Jack, Blackie, Guild Press Ltd., RC 101, 1971 (Box 27)
- Evans, Jack, Like Father, Like Son, Guild Press Ltd., RC 103, 1971 (Box 27)
- Evans, Jack, Back Stage Stud, Guild Press Ltd., RC 104, 1971 (Box 27)
- Evans, Jack, All The Studs At Sea, Guild Press Ltd., RC 105, 1971 (Box 28)
- Evans, Jack, Art Pupil, Guild Press Ltd., RC 107, 1971 (Box 28)
- Evans, Jack, Buzzy, Guild Press Ltd., RC 116, 1971 (Box 28)
- Evans, Jack, A Day Of Glory, Guild Press Ltd., RC 120, 1971 (Box 28)
- Evans, Jack, Home Is Where The Hard Is, Monkey Pubn., MP 1269-1, 1969 (Box 36)
- Evans, Jack, The Gay Ship Lollypop, Monkey Pubn., MP 170-1, 1969 (Box 36)
- Evans, Jack, Biker's Boy, Rough Trade, RT411, n.d. (Box 90)
- Evans, Jack, Leather Boys, Rough Trade, RT402, n.d. (Box 90)
- Everhard, Pete, Little Boy Ball-Buster, Star Dist., WB 121, 1976 (Box 68)
- Everts, Tag, The Jock Pot, GX, Inc., TC 223, n.d. (Box 30)
- Everts, Tag, Pay Twenty-One, GX, Inc., TC 225, n.d. (Box 30)
- Everts, Tag, Come Nine, GX, Inc., TC 229, n.d. (Box 30)
- Everts, Tag, Heads Are Winners, GX, Inc., TC 234, n.d. (Box 30)
- Everts, Tag, Hard Ten, GX, Inc., TC 237, n.d. (Box 30)
- Exander, Max, Safestud, Alyson, -0-, 1985 (Box 1)
- Exander, Max, Mansex And Othe Stories, Gay Sunshine Press, -0-, 1985 (Box 93)
- Faber, Jon, Dick Duty, Rough Trade, RT 473, 1979 (Box 56)
- Fadiman, Edwin Jr., The 21" Screen, Signet Books, S 1716, 1958 (Box 57)
- Fair, Alan, The New Boy, Greenleaf Classics, PR 302, 1971 (Box 46)
- Fair, Alan, The Boys In Olive Drag, Phenix Publishers, CB 559, 1968 (Box 43)
- Fair, Alan, A Man's Affair, Phenix Publishers, CB 563, 1968 (Box 43)
- Fair, Alan, The Lover-Boys, Phenix Publishers, LL 759, 1968 (Box 44)
- Fair, Alan, Villa Of Queens, Phenix Publishers, CB 555, 1968 (Box 43)
- Falkon, Felix Lance, Nine Easy Pieces, Greenleaf Classics, PR 309, 1971 (Box 46)
- Falkon, Felix Lance, Hung In Space, Phenix Publishers, PR 233, 1969 (Box 44)
- Falkon, Felix Lance, Castration Castle, Phenix Publishers, PR 264, 1970 (Box 45)
- Falzar, San, Boy-Hungry Aristocrats, Star Dist., Club 126, 1973 (Box 60)
- Falzar, San, The Virgin Cadet, Star Dist., SPADE 143, 1974 (Box 66)
- Fanning, Dick, Bisexual Boy, Continental Classics, CC-244, 1969 (Box 90)
- Farout, Billy, A Sailor Coming Out, Parisian Press, P 209, 1972 (Box 41)
- Farout, Billy, The Chauffeur Did It, Parisian Press, P 217, 1972 (Box 42)
- Farout, Billy, Fresh From The Farm, Parisian Press, P 224, 1972 (Box 42)
- Farout, Billy, Man, It Must Be Heaven, Parisian Press, P 228, 1972 (Box 42)
- Farout, Billy, Hero In The Bedroom, Parisian Press, P 237, 1972 (Box 42)
- Farr, Kelton, His Secret Life, Triumph, TNC 316, 1968 (Box 87)
- Farrell, Henry, What Ever Happened To Baby Jane?, Avon, G-1146, 1960 (Box 5)
- Farris, John, Harrison High, Dell, 3448, 1959 (Box 15)
- Faulk, Guy, It's A Gay, Gay World, Guild Press Ltd., TC102, 1968 (Box 28)
- Faulk, Jerry, A Real Gone Goose, Guild Press Ltd., TC110, 1968 (Box 28)
- Faulk, Jerry, What Now My Love?, Guild Press Ltd., TC120, 1969 (Box 28)
- Faulk, Jerry, Goose Gone Gander, Guild Press Ltd., TC122, 1969 (Box 28)
- Faulk, Jerry, A Real Gone Goose, Guild Press Ltd., TC110, 1968 (Box 28)
- Fawkes, Guy, Chamber Of Homos, P. E. C., FL 94, 1970 (Box 52)
- Febick, Walter, Apprentice Gay, Lambda Press, LB 106, 1974 (Box 33)
- Fenster, Percy, Hot Pants Homo, All Star Books, AS-22, 1964 (Box 1)
- Ferren, George, The Butt Branders, Star Dist., Club 131, 1974 (Box 60)
- Ferren, George, Dude Ranch Suckers, Star Dist., Club 134, 1974 (Box 60)
- Ferren, George, Let My Boys Come, Star Dist., HS 1008, 1975 (Box 62)
- Ferren, George, The Meat-Eater Millionaire, Star Dist., SPADE 137, 1974 (Box 66)
- Fey, Edwin, Summer In Sodom, Paperback Library, 54-808, 1964 (Box 41)
- Fielding, Hank, The Dew Drop Kid, Blueboy Library, BB 120, 1978 (Box 11)
- Fields, Bruce, My Man - My Lover, Arena, MP 115, 1984 (Box 2)
- Fields, Bruce, Dark & Dangerous, Arena, MP 126, 1984 (Box 3)
- Fils, Crebillion, My Bachelor's Life, Belmont Books, B75-213, 1966 (Box 6)
- Fitzgerald, Frank, Gay Male Nurse, Barclay House, 7094, 1970 (Box 6)
- Fletcher, O. J., Reamout!, Surrey House, HIS 06988, 1974 (Box 71)
- Fletcher, O. J., Bunghole Buddies, Surrey House, MH 426, 1973 (Box 81)
- Flinders, Karl, Up Daddy, Olympia Press, TC-508, 1971 (Box 39)
- Flinders, Karl, The Boy Avengers, Olympia Press, TC-516, 1971 (Box 39)
- Flinders, Karl, Twelve Inches Around The World, Ophelia Press, OPH-237, 1971 (Box 40)
- Floyd, Bill May, Saturday Night Fervor, Blueboy Library, BB 101, 1978 (Box 11)
- Floyd, Harvey, Able-Bodied,, -0-, n.d. (Box 93)
- Forbes, Jason, Two, Bark Book, -0-, 1969 (Box 6)
- Forbes, Jason, Cream For Dessert, Book House, BH 102, 1969 (Box 12)
- Forbes, Jason, All-Nite Sucker, Book House, BH 104, 1969 (Box 12)
- Forbes, Jason, My First Million Inches, Greenleaf Classics, GL 137, 1969 (Box 26)
- Forbes, Jason, The Rap For Sodomy, Greenleaf Classics, GL 157, 1969 (Box 26)
- Forbes, Jason, The Happy Hustler, Lambda Press, LB 102, 1974 (Box 33)
- Forbes, Jason, Made In England, Phenix Publishers, PR 255, 1970 (Box 45)
- Forbes, Jason, Barry And The Burglars, Phenix Publishers, PR 268, 1970 (Box 45)
- Forbes, Jason, Cockalorum, Phenix Publishers, PR 281, 1970 (Box 46)
- Forbes, Jason, Get It Up, Phenix Publishers, PR 291, 1970 (Box 46)
- Forbes, Lyle, The Last Affair, Greenleaf Classics, PR 344, 1972 (Box 47)
- Forbes, Lyle, Colt For Hire, Greenleaf Classics, PR 365, 1972 (Box 48)
- Ford, Christopher, Baby Stud, GX, Inc., GH 2002, n.d. (Box 28)
- Ford, Christopher, The Red Headed Wipe Out, GX, Inc., TC 258, 1973 (Box 31)
- Ford, Christopher, The Tv Star, P. E. C., FL 100, 1971 (Box 53)
- Ford, Christopher, Inside Out, P. E. C., FL 99, 1971 (Box 53)
- Ford, Christopher, El Rubio, XXX Inc., GW 113, 1971 (Box 18)
- Ford, Christopher, Christopher's Craft, XXX Inc., GW 116, 1971 (Box 18)
- Ford, Christopher, Christopher's Phallusies, XXX Inc., GW 119, 1971 (Box 18)
- Ford, Christopher, 'Midst Pleasures And Phalluses, XXX Inc., GW 126, n.d. (Box 18)
- Ford, Christopher, Laguna Rip Off, FS Publishing, Inc., GW 109, n.d. (Box 90)
- Foreman, Gil, Locker Room Lover, Surree Ltd, SS 048, 1978 (Box 85)
- Forest, Jerry, Going Door To Door, Publisher's Consultants, BAB 110, 1978 (Box 49)
- Fortune, Walter, Dallas Pretty Boy, Publisher's Consultants, BAB 111, 1978 (Box 49)
- Foster, Frank, Bossman's Playthings, Star Dist., CC-105, 1977 (Box 59)
- Foster, Greg, Say, Mister!, Greenleaf Classics, PR 353, 1972 (Box 47)
- Fox, Alan, Fickle And Gay, P. E. C., FL 52, 1968 (Box 51)
- Fox, Alan, The Lonely Boy, P. E. C., FL 55, 1969 (Box 51)
- Fox, John, Blowing In The Wind, Gay World Special, -0-, n.d. (Box 19)
- Foxx, Warren, Plug-In Stud, Surrey House, HIS 06989, 1974 (Box 71)
- Francis, Julian, Bunny Bitch, Greenleaf Classics, GL 131, 1969 (Box 26)
- Francis, Julian, Bonny Sweet Robin, Phenix Publishers, PR 249, 1970 (Box 45)
- Frank, Harry, Up Your Alley, Surrey House, HIS 06963, 1973 (Box 71)
- Frank, Harry, Come Quick!, Surrey House, HIS 06985, 1974 (Box 71)
- Frank, Jerry, He Whore, XXX Inc., GW 120, 1971 (Box 18)
- Franklin, Harvey, Cocksure Country Boy, Star Dist., BD 1010, 1976 (Box 59)
- Franklin, Jerry, Held For Ransom, Arena, MP 157, 1985 (Box 3)
- Frazier, Bob, Coming Out, 101 Enterprises, 101-30, 1968 (Box 40)
- Fredericks, Carl, The Traveling Sexman, Parisian Press, P 241, 1972 (Box 42)
- Freiden, Donald, The Boys In The Bund, GX, Inc., SB 601, 1973 (Box 28)
- Fremoni, J., Gay Blades, Eros Publishing, GGS-101, 1973 (Box 16)
- Frey, Gerrold, Ronnie, Phenix Publishers, PR 286, 1970 (Box 46)
- Fritscher, Jack, Leather Blues, Gay Sunshine Press, -0-, 1984 (Box 93)
- Gaellis, Jackson, Uniformed Rape, Star Dist., SS-1011, 1976 (Box 66)
- Gamlin, Douglas H., Homosexual Incest, Phenix Publishers, LL 769, 1968 (Box 44)
- Garbo, Edward, Double Truckin', Surrey House, MH 454, 1974 (Box 82)
- Garcin, Jerry, The Stud Hustler, K.D.S., 073, 1969 (Box 33)
- Garfield, Dick, His Black Adonis, Cameo Library, 928039, 1970 (Box 13)
- Garfield, Dick, Tearoom Castles, GX, Inc., TC 202, 1971 (Box 29)
- Garfield, Dick, The Tatooed Lovers, GX, Inc., SP 104, 1972 (Box 29)
- Garfield, Dick, Men Of The Susquehanna, GX, Inc., SP 109, 1973 (Box 29)
- Garfield, Dick, Mardi Gras Madness, GX, Inc., TC 264, 1973 (Box 31)
- Garfield, Dick, The Chicken & The Hawks, GX, Inc., TC 268, 1973 (Box 32)
- Garfield, Dick, Island Heat, GX, Inc., TC 274, 1973 (Box 32)
- Garfield, Dick, Dark Brothers, GX, Inc., TC 277, 1973 (Box 32)
- Garfield, Dick, Unlikely Lovers, GX, Inc., TC 281, 1973 (Box 32)
- Garfield, Dick, Sea Sucker, Surree Ltd, HIS 69225, 1978 (Box 76)
- Garland, Rodney, The Heart In Exile, Pyramid Books, X 1344, 1953 (Box 53)
- Garner, Leland, Tops, Bottoms And Sidepockets, Foremost Publishers, CL 7, 1965 (Box 17)
- Garnett, Gabe, Tight-End Ream, Surrey House, HIS 69120, 1974 (Box 72)
- Garrett, Dave, The Second Coming, GX, Inc., SP 120, 1973 (Box 29)
- Garrett, Dave, The Seed Seekers, GX, Inc., TC 252, 1973 (Box 31)
- Garrison, Grady, Cummin' Out, Surrey House, HIS 06999, 1974 (Box 72)
- Garvin, Ed, Trickin' & Truckin', Surrey House, HIS 06966, 1973 (Box 71)
- Gay, Robert A., Pagan Male, Nordisk Bladcentral, SVEA 12, 1968 (Box 36)
- Gay, Robert A., Friends And Lovers, Nordisk Bladcentral, SVEA 33, 1969 (Box 36)
- Gay, Robert A., Rendezvous-For Men Only, Nordisk Bladcentral, SVEA 54, n.d. (Box 36)
- Gaylord, James, Queer Street, Bee-Line, 391-N, 1969 (Box 6)
- Geis, Alex, The Prick Of The Picador, P. E. C., FL 59, 1969 (Box 52)
- Geis, Alex, Jailhouse Queen, P. E. C., FL 63, 1969 (Box 52)
- Geis, Alex, Male Bride, P. E. C., FL 80, 1970 (Box 52)
- Genet, Jean, The Thief's Journal, Bantam Books, N 3046, 1949 (Box 5)
- Genet, Jean, Our Lady Of The Flowers, Bantam Books, 02945, 1964 (Box 6)
- Genet, Jean, The Thief's Journal, Olympia Press, no. 78, 1954 (Box 38)
- Genet, Jean, Our Lady Of The Flowers, Olympia Press, no. 36, n.d. (Box 38)
- Genet, Stephen, Whipped Cream, Brandon House, 6124, 1970 (Box 95)
- George, Franz, Tied Chicken, Surree Ltd, HIS 69159, 1976 (Box 73)
- George, Franz, Black In White, Surree Ltd, HIS 69174, 1976 (Box 74)
- George, Fred, Cocky Cousins, Surrey House, HIS 69124, 1974 (Box 72)
- George, Fred, Tricky Dick, Surrey House, HIS 69125, 1974 (Box 72)
- Gibson, Daniel, Well Hung-Up, Surrey House, HIS 06940, 1972 (Box 70)
- Gifford, Lon, Hard-On The Saddle, Surrey House, MH 469, 1974 (Box 82)
- Gilbert, Dan, All Dick!, Surrey House, HIS 06997, 1974 (Box 72)
- Gilbert, Daniel, Through The Chute, Surrey House, HIS 06979, 1974 (Box 71)